Creating your business identity in English.
-- 用英語創造您的企業形象。
You’re ready to focus on some business English, which means we need to start by looking at how greetings can be different, and when I say different, I mean generally more formal, but not always!
-- 你已經準備好專注於一些商務英語，這意味著我們需要先看看問候語如何不同，當我說不同時，我的意思是通常更正式，但並非總是如此！
You’re also going to learn great vocabulary, idioms and about business culture in the US so you can feel comfortable working with Americans.
-- 您還將學習豐富的詞彙、習慣用語和美國的商業文化，這樣您就可以輕鬆地與美國人一起工作。
What we’ll do now is translate the business skills and confidence you have from your native language into English so that you are taken seriously!
-- 我們現在要做的就是將您所擁有的商業技能和信心從您的母語翻譯成英語，以便您受到認真對待！
To take someone seriously means to respect someone and view them as important. And you deserve respect for all the hard work you’ve been doing to improve your English.
-- 認真對待某人意味著尊重某人並認為他們很重要。你為提高英語水平所做的所有努力都值得尊重。
Let’s get started and look at greetings. Business greetings.
-- 商務問候。
When you are not greeting a friend or family member, the most important question to ask yourself is, “What is my relationship with this person?” Because, depending on the type of work you do, you don’t always want to be formal. If you appear too formal, you’ll look and sound like a robot, which means you will appear inauthentic.
-- 當你不跟朋友或家人打招呼時，要問自己的最重要的問題是：“我和這個人的關係是什麼？”因為，根據您從事的工作類型，您並不總是希望保持正式。如果你顯得太正式，你看起來和聽起來就像機器人，這意味著你會顯得不真實。
Inauthentic means fake, not honest. And the type of business English you need might even change throughout the day, so in every situation ask yourself, “What business identity do I need for this moment?” Is it a serious meeting with the board of directors or a casual lunch with a client where you need to appear relaxed and friendly while drinking a beer?
-- 不真實的意思是假的，不誠實的。您需要的商務英語類型甚至可能會在一天中發生變化，因此在每種情況下都要問自己：“此時此刻我需要什麼商務身份？”這是與董事會的嚴肅會議，還是與客戶的休閒午餐，您需要在喝啤酒時表現出輕鬆和友好？
Let’s start with formal greetings and then move onto casual greetings so you can speak English with dignity and command respect in any type of business conversation.
-- 讓我們從正式問候開始，然後轉向休閒問候，這樣您就可以在任何類型的商務對話中有尊嚴地說英語並贏得尊重。
Formal Greetings.
-- 正式的問候。
I recommend formal greetings with people you are meeting for the first time, don’t know well, and with anyone who is in a more senior position.
-- 我建議您與第一次見面、不熟悉的人以及任何職位較高的人進行正式的問候。
Meeting someone for the first time.
-- 第一次見到某人。
When you meet someone in person for the first time, you have a few options.“Hello, Mr. so-and-so. Nice to meet you.”
-- 當你第一次見到某人時，你有幾個選擇。很高興見到你。
So that’s for a man and we use their last name. For women it’s a little trickier, because women have two titles.
-- 這是一個男人的名字，我們使用他們的姓氏。對於女性來說，這有點棘手，因為女性有兩個頭銜。
‘Ms.’ if she is unmarried and ‘Mrs.’ is she is married. So if you are meeting a woman for the first time, do your research before you meet her so you know which title to use.
-- 如果她未婚，則使用「女士」；如果她已婚，則使用「女士」。因此，如果您是第一次見到一位女士，請在見到她之前先進行研究，以便知道該使用哪個頭銜。
“Hello, Ms. so-and-so. Nice to meet you.” “Hello, Mrs. so-and-so. Nice to meet you.”
-- “您好，某某女士。很高興見到你。 “您好，某某女士。很高興見到你。
So ‘Ms.’ sounds like“miss” and ‘Mrs.’ sounds like ‘misses’.
-- 所以“Ms.”聽起來像“miss”，“Mrs.”聽起來像“misss”。
We use “so-and-so” when we are giving examples and the person’s name isn’t important. Like here, I wanted you to focus on the titles showing if a woman is married or not. You can also use it when you’re telling a story and forget someone’s name.*
-- 當我們舉例時，我們會使用“某某”，而這個人的名字並不重要。就像在這裡，我希望您專注於顯示女性是否已婚的標題。當您在講故事並忘記某人的名字時也可以使用它。
If you don’t know if a woman is married, it’s probably better to avoid saying her last name and just say, “Hello. Nice to meet you.”
-- 如果你不知道一位女性是否已婚，最好不要說出她的姓氏，而只是說：「你好。很高興見到你。
Using the wrong title when meeting a woman can be insulting. Because generally, Mrs. is for married women or older women. Ms. is for younger women or single women.
--與女性見面時使用錯誤的稱呼可能會造成侮辱。因為一般來說，Mrs.是指已婚婦女或老年婦女。 Ms. 適合年輕女性或單身女性。